<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ballegend</string>
    <string name="the_greatests_ever">THE GREATESTS EVER</string>
    <string name="messi">Lionel Messi</string>
    <string name="c_ronaldo">Cristiano Ronaldo</string>
    <string name="pele">Edson Arantes do Nascimento (Pele)</string>
    <string name="maradonna">Diego Maradona</string>
    <string name="cruyff">Johan Cruyff</string>
    <string name="puskas">Ferenc Puskas</string>
    <string name="beckenbauer">\t\Franz Beckenbauer</string>
    <string name="zidane">Zinedine Zidane</string>
    <string name="r_ronaldo">Nazario Ronaldo</string>
    <string name="stefano">Alfredo Di Stefano</string>
    <string name="platini">Michel Platini</string>
    <string name="muller">Gerd Müller</string>
    <string name="maldini">Paolo Maldini</string>
    <string name="baresi">Franco Baresi</string>
    <string name="kaka">Ricardo Izecson dos Santos Leite (Kaká)</string>
    <string name="van_basten">Marco van Basten</string>
    <string name="bobby">Sir Bobby Charlton</string>
    <string name="yashin">Lev Yashin</string>
    <string name="ronaldiho">Ronaldinho Gaúcho</string>
    <string name="iniesta">Andres Iniesta</string>
    <string name="xavi">Xavier Hernández Creus(Xavi)</string>
    <string name="bale">Gareth Bale</string>
    <string name="gullit">Ruud Gullit</string>
    <string name="best">George Best</string>
    <string name="garrincha">Manuel Francisco dos Santos(Garrincha)</string>
    <string name="eusebio">Eusébio da Silva Ferreira</string>
    <string name="zico">Arthur Antunes Coimbra (Zico)</string>
    <string name="meazza">Giuseppe Meazza</string>
    <string name="baggio">Roberto Baggio</string>
    <string name="henry">Thierry Henry</string>
    <string name="modric">Luka Modric</string>
    <string name="modric_description">The Croatian midfield maestro, orchestrated the midfield with his intelligence and precise passing, leading Croatia to the World Cup final in 2018 and winning numerous domestic and European titles with Real Madrid, earning the Ballon d\'Or in 2018.</string>
    <string name="henry_description">The goal-scoring sensation, combined lightning speed with exquisite technique to become Arsenal\'s all-time leading scorer and win numerous league titles and individual awards, cementing his status as one of the Premier League\'s greatest players.</string>
    <string name="baggio_description">" The Italian maestro, mesmerized with his elegant dribbling and clinical finishing, earning the nickname \"Il Divin Codino\" (The Divine Ponytail) and leaving an unforgettable imprint on the game, despite his heartbreaking penalty miss in the 1994 World Cup final."</string>
    <string name="meazza_description">He, showcased his brilliance with Internazionale and Italy, leading his country to two World Cup triumphs and leaving a lasting legacy as one of the most revered figures in Italian football history.</string>
    <string name="eusebio_description">The \"Black Panther\" from Portugal, thrilled fans with his explosive speed and lethal finishing, winning the Ballon d\'Or in 1965 and leaving an indelible mark as one of the greatest goal-scorers in history.</string>
    <string name="garrincha_description">enchanted the world with his magical dribbling and unmatched skill, helping Brazil to two World Cup victories and becoming a symbol of joy and creativity on the football pitch.</string>
    <string name="best_description">Northern Irish genius, mesmerized crowds with his dazzling dribbling and instinctive goal-scoring ability, earning the nickname the \"Fifth Beatle\" and leaving an enduring legacy as one of the greatest players of all time.</string>
    <string name="gullit_description">Blended power and finesse to become one of football\'s most complete players, leading AC Milan to back-to-back European Cup triumphs and earning the Ballon d\'Or in 1987.</string>
    <string name="bale_description">" Soared to new heights with his blistering pace and remarkable athleticism, showcasing his talent in memorable moments such as his stunning goals in Champions League finals and his electrifying performances for both club and country."</string>
    <string name="xavi_description">The metronome of Barcelona\'s midfield, epitomized precision and intelligence, guiding his team to numerous domestic and international titles, including three Champions League trophies, with his masterful passing and tactical brilliance.</string>
    <string name="iniesta_description">" Spanish midfield maestro, orchestrated countless triumphs for both Barcelona and Spain, including multiple La Liga titles and a World Cup victory in 2010, displaying unparalleled vision and composure on the ball."</string>
    <string name="ronaldiho_description">" Magician, dazzled with his mesmerizing skills and infectious smile, earning two FIFA World Player of the Year awards. A strong contender for greatest dribbler of alltimes, and left and indelible mark on the world of football."</string>
    <string name="Baressi_description">The defensive cornerstone of AC Milan\'s legendary squad. He epitomized elegance and resilience in his play. With numerous Serie A titles and European Cup triumphs, his leadership and skill at the heart of the defense made him one of the finest defenders of his generation.</string>
    <string name="maldini_description">Commanded the pitch with grace and tenacity. With seven Serie A titles and five Champions League triumphs, he embodied AC Milan\'s golden era, earning universal acclaim as one of the greatest defenders in football history.</string>
    <string name="lev_description">the Soviet goalkeeper known as the \"Black Spider\", revolutionized his position, winning the Ballon d\'Or in 1963 and leaving a legacy of unmatched shot-stopping prowess.</string>
    <string name="bobby_description">The English midfield dynamo, lifted the World Cup in 1966 and remains Manchester United\'s all-time leading goal scorer.</string>
    <string name="basten_desxription">The marksman, showcased exquisite technique, securing three Ballon d\'Or titles and scoring unforgettable goals.</string>
    <string name="kaka_description">" Brazilian playmaker, mesmerized with his skill and speed, winning the Ballon d'Or in 2007 and leading AC Milan to Champions League triumph."</string>
    <string name="muller_description">" German goal-scoring machine, amassed over 700 career goals, including the winner in the 1974 World Cup final."</string>
    <string name="platini_description">" The maestro, orchestrated midfield mastery, claiming three Ballon d'Or awards and leading France to European Championship glory."</string>
    <string name="stephano_description">The Argentine-Spanish legend, epitomized versatility, leadership, and brilliance. With five consecutive European Cup titles, over 300 goals, and unmatched intelligence on the field, he stands as one of football\'s greatest icons, shaping the sport\'s history and inspiring generations with his remarkable talent.\n\n\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="nazario">The Phenomenon, mesmerizes with his explosive pace and clinical finishing, amassing over 400 career goals and earning two FIFA World Player of the Year awards, leaving a legacy of pure talent and unforgettable moments that define him as one of the greatest strikers to grace the game.</string>
    <string name="zidane_description">The French virtuoso renowned for his sublime skill and unparalleled vision, delivers moments of brilliance on the grandest stages, including his iconic World Cup final performance in 1998 and three FIFA World Player of the Year awards, elevating him to the pantheon of footballing greatness.</string>
    <string name="beckenbauer_description">The German \'Kaiser\', dominates the game with a rare blend of strength and finesse, winning three European Cups with Bayern Munich and lifting the FIFA World Cup as both player and coach, solidifying his status as one of the most influential figures in football history.</string>
    <string name="puskas_description">The Hungarian icon, leaves defenders in awe with his prolific scoring prowess, amassing over 700 career goals and leading Hungary\'s \'Magical Magyars\' to unprecedented success, forever enshrining his legacy as one of football\'s true legends.</string>
    <string name="cruyff_description">" Maestro credited with revolutionizing the game with his innovative \"Total Football\" philosophy, graces the pitch with unmatched elegance and intelligence, earning three Ballon d'Or titles and leaving an indelible mark on the sport as both player and manager."</string>
    <string name="maradonna_description">Revered for his iconic \'Hand of God\' and \'Goal of the Century\', alongside a FIFA World Cup triumph in 1986, transcends the sport with his mesmerizing skill and captivating charisma, forever etching his name among football\'s immortals.</string>
    <string name="pele_description">It is he, with three FIFA World Cup victories and more than 1,000 career goals, embodies the essence of Brazilian flair and excellence, leaving an enduring legacy as one of the most prolific and beloved players in history.</string>
    <string name="ronaldo_description">suiii! oasting over 800 career goals and five UEFA Champions League titles, showcases relentless athleticism and unmatched determination, cementing his status as a global icon in the world of football.</string>
    <string name="messi_description">M10, with over 700 career goals and a record-breaking eight Ballon d\'Or awards, mesmerizes with his graceful dribbling and pinpoint accuracy, earning him recognition as one of the greatest footballers of all time.</string>
    <string name="zico_description">The Brazilian maestro, captured numerous titles with Flamengo, including four Campeonato Brasileiro Série A titles and the Copa Libertadores in 1981. Internationally, he starred in three World Cups and earned three South American Footballer of the Year awards, leaving an enduring legacy in football history.</string>
    <string name="greatests_of_time">GREATESTS OF TIME</string>
    <string name="the_best_there_was_all_worthy_some_many_times_over">The Best There Was, All Worthy, Some Many Times Over</string>
</resources>